[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]
And we have now seen how to build a decision tree from data.
ولقد رأينا الآن كيفية إنشاء شجرة قرارات باستخدام البيانات.
It's pretty cool, simple, really recursive algorithm,
فهي خوارزمية رائعة وبسيطة ومتكررة للغاية.
main choice to be made is what feature to split on and when to stop splitting.
والاختيار الأساسي الذي يجب القيام به، هو حول ما السمة التي يجب التقسيم على أساسها ومتى يتوقف التقسيم.
In the next module we're going to talk about ways to address over fitting
وفي الوحدة القادمة سنتحدث حول طرق التعامل مع الإفراط في المطابقة
in decision trees.
في أشجار القرارات.
But you should be ready now to understand how to build a decision tree from data,
ولكن يجب أن تكون مستعدًا الآن لفهم كيفية إنشاء شجرة القرارات باستخدام البيانات،
really implement that algorithm, and
وتطبيق هذه الخوارزمية،
be able to make predictions from the decision trees that you learn.
وتكون قادرًا على إجراء التنبؤات من أشجار القرارات التي تتعلمها.
As well as to explore decision boundaries of decision trees and
كذلك لاستكشاف حدود القرار لأشجار القرارات
how they relate to decision boundaries of say logistic regression.
وكيف تتعلق بحدود القرارات والانحدار اللوجستي.
And let me close by thanking my colleague
ودعوني أختتم ذلك بشكر زميلي
Krishna who was instrumental in making the slides that you saw in this module.
كريشنا الذي كان له دور هام في عمل تلك الشرائح التي رأيتموها في هذه الوحدة.
I really appreciate all the effort that Krishna put into this.
أنا حقًا أقدر كل تلك المجهودات التي قام بها كريشنا لإنجاز ذلك.
[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]